<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fish.farmR</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on fish.farmR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About fish.farmR</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is an open notebook that is focused on the application of R-based tools to gather and explore data sets that may be relevant to aquaculture operations, finance, and economics. We will look at the global situation as well as the scale of the farm, as we are lead by our interests. I suppose there will be ample opportunity to stray about between scales of analysis.
I would say confidently that I identify mostly with what I don&#39;t know about this topic and less with what I do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello all and welcome!</title>
      <link>/2019/12/21/hello-all-and-welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/12/21/hello-all-and-welcome/</guid>
      <description>Yo!Well isn’t this lovely! I get to pretend that I’m talking to the entire world. And yet I don’t want to speak to the whole world, I want to speak only to you, the person who wants to know more about world of aquaculture data analysis and visualization. I am so glad that you are here! We will have fun learning about this fascinating and growing ecosystem of information and real actions on the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STECF data download and inspect (part_1)</title>
      <link>/2019/12/21/stecf-data-download-and-exploration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/12/21/stecf-data-download-and-exploration/</guid>
      <description>purposeDownload and take an intial look at the European Commisson,Fisheries and Aquaculture: Scientific, Technical and Economic Committee for Fisheries (STECF) aquaculture economic data tables.
analyst noteThis is part 1. As I move through the stages of exploration, and when I feel like it might be worth sharing with you, I’ll post another part. Each part will include data and package load steps, so that they can be more stand-alone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>